

NGUYEN MINH VU

+84 905 039 118 minhvu.domus@gmail.com Thanh Khe, Danang DOB: 09/26/1994

OBJECTIVE

I had one and a half-year experience working for Engineering Company at Project Department Specialist and Vice Project Department Manager, 6 months working as Sale & Marketing Manager and Branch Manager at Jello Academy in HCM city. During the time in the university, I had 2 internships at Vinacapital Danang and Zalora Vietnam. Moreover, I won 2 prizes in Marketing and Start-up Contests held by Sunwah Vietnam and Doanh Nhan Sai Gon Magazine. One plus point is that I had an IELTS 7.0 certificate in 2013, which showed the strength of reading and listening skills. Now, I really love to find a job that gives me not only opportunities but also challenges.

BEST 5 SKILLS AND ABILITIES

- ✓ Develop business
- ✓ Working Attitude and Willingness to Learn
- ✓ Responsibility
- ✓ Creative, Innovative
- ✓ Presentation

LANGUAGE

English: Advanced (IELTS 7.0 in 2013)

Vietnamese: Native

EXPERIENCE

VINACAPITAL DANANG

06/2013 – 09/2013 Accounting Department Intern

ZALORA VIETNAM

06/2015 – 09/2015 Partnership Department Intern

PETECH ENGINEERING CORPORATION, HOCHIMINH

02/2017 - 05/2018

Project Development Department Specialist, Deputy Manager of Project Development Department

- ✓ Creating good connection with foreign partners
- ✓ Planning and applying motivated ideas to develop the business
- ✓ Importing goods for manufacturing
- ✓ Learning and applying modern methods to improve the business performance
- ✓ Negotiate with Government Departments

JELLO ACADEMY, HOCHIMINH

2018

Sale & Marketing Manager, Branch Manager

- ✓ Developing the business in Hochiminh for the 6-months project.
- ✓ Building the strategy for sale, recruiting sale team members
- ✓ Reaching the target for sale in the Southern Market
- ✓ Build the database for sales, included more than 300 potential customers

DREAM TALENTS, HOCHIMINH

2019

Sale Leader – Elite Team

- ✓ Reaching the Vietnamese-American Customers via Phone
- ✓ Creating good relationship, close sale
- ✓ Leading online sale team for life insurances

AIA, DANANG

2021

Personal Financial Adviser

Updated 12.2020

NGUYEN MINH VU

+84 905 039 118 MINHVU.DOMUS@GMAIL.COM THANH KHE, DANANG DOB: 09/26/1994

EDUCATION

VIETNAMESE AND GERMAN UNIVERSITY

Bachelor, majoring Finance and Accounting, 09/2012 – 12/2016.

VCCI - COURSE

How to create production plan, 2018.

BMG EDUCATION

Trade marketing, 2016.

WORK@SAIGON

Creative Concept, 2015.

AWARDS

- ✓ Creative Prize in the marketing contest held by Sunwah Group in 2014.
- √ 4th Prize in Start-up Contests held by Doanh Nhan Sai Gon Magazine in 2016.
- ✓ Scholarship for 30% of tuition fee in 2012

EXTRAS

- ✓ Head of Sale & Marketing team which held the Pool Party 2015 for University Students in Binh Duong
- ✓ Head of Data team, which help to create the very first database for the library of the university